{
    "subject": "resource/James_Madison",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Port_Conway,_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "James Madison was born in Port Conway, Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8060371279716492,
            "question": "Where was James Madison born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4558568298816681,
            "question": "What state is Port Conway in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2600608766078949,
            "question": "What political party was James Madison associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2456780970096588,
            "question": "James Madison was a key figure in which historical period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22100482881069183,
            "question": "James Madison is often referred to as the '_____' because of his role in shaping the Constitution."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2110614776611328,
            "question": "What university did James Madison attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14749380946159363,
            "question": "What role did James Madison play in the American Revolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.131130650639534,
            "question": "James Madison served as the _____ president of the United States."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10199896991252899,
            "question": "What important document did James Madison help draft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.030923008918762207,
            "question": "Who was the author of the Federalist Papers along with Alexander Hamilton and John Jay?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Madison was born in Port Conway, Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6872_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What important document did James Madison help draft?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6872_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Madison served as the _____ president of the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6872_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did James Madison play in the American Revolution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6872_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6872_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple instances that confirm James Madison's birthplace as Port Conway, Virginia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently provide information about James Madison's birthplace as Port Conway, Virginia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}